{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Door Painters","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62414/":{"taskOID":62414,"originalTaskOID":62414,"setID":8928,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5069,"questionDisplayText":"Type of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6001,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain","answerDisplayText":"Stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500845,"questionDisplayText":"Painting Needs:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be painted?","shortQuestionText":"What needs to be painted?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3319,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Interior door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2658,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Front door","answerDisplayText":"Front door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":921,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Back door","answerDisplayText":"Back door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2317,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Exterior door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Exterior door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2008,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Door frame","answerDisplayText":"Door frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5072,"questionDisplayText":"New color","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will the new color be:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lighter than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Lighter than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1829,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Darker than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Darker than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Same or similar to existing color","answerDisplayText":"Same or similar to existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4000,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Multiple colors","answerDisplayText":"Multiple colors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5069,"questionDisplayText":"Type of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6001,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain","answerDisplayText":"Stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6001,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain","answerDisplayText":"Stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500845,"questionDisplayText":"Painting Needs:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be painted?","shortQuestionText":"What needs to be painted?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3319,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Interior door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2658,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Front door","answerDisplayText":"Front door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":921,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Back door","answerDisplayText":"Back door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2317,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Exterior door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Exterior door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2008,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Door frame","answerDisplayText":"Door frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3319,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Interior door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2658,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Front door","answerDisplayText":"Front door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":921,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Back door","answerDisplayText":"Back door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2317,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Exterior door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Exterior door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2008,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Door frame","answerDisplayText":"Door frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5072,"questionDisplayText":"New color","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will the new color be:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lighter than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Lighter than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1829,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Darker than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Darker than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Same or similar to existing color","answerDisplayText":"Same or similar to existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4000,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Multiple colors","answerDisplayText":"Multiple colors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lighter than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Lighter than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1829,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Darker than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Darker than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Same or similar to existing color","answerDisplayText":"Same or similar to existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4000,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Multiple colors","answerDisplayText":"Multiple colors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/62414/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62414,"taskName":"Painting or Staining - Doors","taskDescription":"Paint or Stain a Door","xmTaskDescriptor":"Door Painters","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"paint, stain, door, door frame","textMessagingName":"Door Paint Proj","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes both interior or exterior. \r\nPainters generally also handle all relevant prep work including washing, scraping, sanding, caulking, patching \u0026 priming. Note separate categories for whole room painting, faux finishes, textured paint, murals, electrostatic painting, refinishing furniture \u0026 popcorn finishes.","rolloverShortDesc":"Interior or exterior doors and door frames","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Paint or Stain an Interior or Exterior Door.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated painters in your area.","htmlTitle":"Interior and Exterior Door Painters \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":55,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Paint or Stain Doors","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Interior or Exterior Painting or Staining - Doors","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Door Painting Project","urlName":"Interior-and-Exterior-Door-Painting","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Interior and Exterior Door Painters in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"paint, stain, painters, painting, door, door frame, doors, interior door, entry door, exterior door","emcCategoryOid":-12054,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":8928,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}